Vasudha Bhalerao, Human Resources Manager

703 Viman co-operative housing society, sector 9A, Gurgaon, 122001, India, 9112264845, bhaleraovasudha4@gmail.com

Date of birth	01/03/1988 Nationality	Indian		
PROFILE	An experienced and dedicated Human Resources Assistant with in-depth knowledge of administrative processe and managing successful relationships with employees. Ability to maintain an organized employee database by collecting records, and carefully organizing paperwork associated with existing and future employees. Adapt in handling personnel related issues, and adhering to laws and regulations governing recruitment and employmen practices.			
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY				
Jun 2020 — Present	Human Resource Manager, Aleta People Services	Gurgaon		
	 Developed and implemented a comprehensive on boarding program that reduced the time to onboard new hires. Established a compensation system that was competitive in the marketplace and attracted top talent Developed and implemented a comprehensive employee engagement survey that identified key areas for improvement in the workplace Created a comprehensive performance management system that improved performance reviews. Developed an employee recognition program that improved employee satisfaction and morale. Developed a comprehensive recruitment plan that reduced time-to-hire. Responsible for end to end recruitment, vendor management, talent management, exit formalities, maintaining data. 			
Jan 2017 — Dec 2018	Project Operation Associate, Drzya	Mumbai		
	 Identified and resolved project issues quickly and efficiently, minimizing their impact on project progress Developed a comprehensive project plan that outlined the key tasks and milestones for a major consulting project, resulting in the successful completion of the project on time and within budget Collaborated with a cross-functional team to develop a new research project, resulting in the successful completion of the project on time and within budget 			
Jul 2023 — Sep 2014	Branch co-ordiantor, Edwise International	Mumbai		
	 Performed daily branch audits to ensure accuracy of customer accounts and cash balances Managed branch operations, including scheduling staff and coordinating customer visits Improved branch compliance with federal regulations, resulting in a reduction in violation Managed students documentation process and their VISA process. 	s		
Jun 2012 — Mar 2013	Relationship Manager, ICICI securities	Mumbai		
	 Created presentations and reports to track customer data and inform stakeholders on customer trends Conducted in-depth customer research to identify new opportunities for growth and expansion Developed and maintained strong relationships with key clients, resulting in increased customer loyalty and satisfaction Resolved customer issues in a timely and efficient manner, resulting in reduction in customer complaints 			
EDUCATION				
Jun 2023 — Present	MBA-HR, Symbiosis institute of management	Pune		
Aug 2010 — May 2012	MBA-Finance, university of Pune	Ahmadnagar		
May 2006 — May 2009	B.com-honors, University of Mumbai			
Jun 2004 — May 2006	H.S.C, Maharashtra State Board			
May 2004 — May 2005	S.S.C, Maharashtra State Board	Mumbai		

SKILLS	Microsoft PowerPoint	Expert	Computer Skills	Expert			
	Communication	Expert	Communication Skills	Expert			
	Leadership	Expert	Program Management	Expert			
	Adaptability	Expert	Training & Development	Expert			
	Microsoft Excel	Expert	Employee Recruitment & Retention	Expert			
	Microsoft Office	Expert					
COURSES Jul 2023 — Jun 2024	POSH certified traine	POSH certified trainer, SKILLDECK - ups killing professional					
LANGUAGES	English	Very good command	Marathi	Highly proficient			
	Hindi	Very good command					
HOBBIES	Reading , playing guitar, sin	nging, reading people's mind	, dancing				

Declaration

I hereby declare that the above mentioned details are true.

Thank you

Vasudha Bhalerao